# Paul Pableo

Toronto, ON | 647- 453-8675 | pableop@gmail.com | LinkedIn | Github | Personal Website

#### FRONT END DEVELOPER SUMMARY

Front-End Web developer with proficiency in developing web applications using React, JavaScript (ES6+), HTML5, CSS3, and API integrations that are interactive, responsive, and web accessible. Previous 10 years of combined experience in Customer Service and Leadership roles with a track record of strong sales outcomes.

- Led team as assistant manager, achieving 60% above target with an annual net of \$3.2M
- Known by team members and classmates for having driving, motivational attitude
- Strong analytical and organizational skills, with a passion for continuous learning

#### **PORTFOLIO PROJECTS**

## Trivia Time (Live | Repo)

- Led a collaborative React Project built utilizing 2 APIs and persistent data via Firebase as real-time database to allow user to save User Avatar, Score, and High Scores
- Utilized 2 REST API data via AJAX request to randomly generate avatar, as well as take user input for Trivia category, and difficulty

# LUX Nail | Beauty Bar (Live | Repo)

- Ecommerce product and service store built with React. Users can browse services, and products, with cart functionality
- Utilized API data for simulated Inventory

# Weather App (Live | Repo)

- Interactive weather app built with OpenWeather API, built with HTML, CSS, and JS
- Fetched OpenWeather API that took User Input for Location Data

# **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

# Assistant Store Manager | Canada Goose

Oct 2016 - Present

- Led team to significant growth in KPI results, achieving 60% above target with a net of 3.2mil in fiscal 2021, and 2022 in addition to reducing store shrinkage to less than 2%
- Increased operational efficiency and inventory management by 20% by reorganizing the physical storage of supplies and layout plan
- Drive Units per Transaction (UPT) by actively introducing new, underperforming, and strategic categories increasing retail sales goal by an average of 20% every quarter in 2022-2023

### **Environmental Service Superior | Trillium Health (Part-Time)**

Jun 2020 - Jun 2021

- Developed positive functional collaborations with 25 different departments to ensure their needs are satisfactorily met; liaises with staff, stakeholders and administrators in developing, planning, implementing and monitoring quality improvement initiatives
- Developed staff and facilitated of daily and ongoing activities ensuring effective use of resources
- Recruited, coached, mentored, evaluated and managed the performance and development of 15 staff

#### **EDUCATION**

Juno College of Technology | Front-End Web Developer Bootcamp Certificate

Jul 2022 - Nov 2022

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, jQuery, React, RESTful API, Firebase, Version control, Git & GitHub